entrylevelminingjob.com.au 2016-05-07

# Privacy Policy - Jobs in Mining

##### Privacy Policy

1\. We respect your privacy  
Jobs In Mining respects your right to privacy and this policy sets out how we collect and treat your personal information.  
“Personal information” is information we hold which is identifiable as being about you.  
2\. What personal information we collect  
We may collect the following types of personal information from you:  
name  
address  
email address  
phone number  
fax number  
information about the goods or services you have ordered  
information from enquiries you have made  
communications between us  
credit card information  
3\. How we collect your personal information  
We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways, including: when you interact with us electronically or in person; when you access our website; and when we provide our services to you.  
4\. Use of your personal information  
We use your information to provide our service to you. We also use it to improve our service and to notify you of opportunities that we think you might be interested in.We do not provide your information to third parties, except that we may provide your information to our business partners who assist us in the provision of our services to you.  
5\. Security of your personal information  
We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However we are not liable for any unauthorised access to this information.  
6\. Access to your personal information  
You can access and update your personal information by contacting us at info@entrylevelminingjob.com.au, we may charge an administration fee for this access.  
7\. Complaints about privacy  
If you have any complaints about our privacy practices, please feel free to send in details of your complaints to info@entrylevelminingjob.com.au. We take complaints very seriously and will respond shortly after receiving written notice of your complaint.  
8\. Changes  
Please be aware that we may change this Privacy Policy in the future. The revised versions will be uploaded onto our website, so please check back from time to time.  
** ** 9 **.** Website  
When you come on to our website we may collect certain information such as browser type, operating system, website visited immediately before coming to our site, etc. This information is used in an aggregated manner to analyse how people use our site, such that we can improve our service.  
Cookies  
As is very common for companies, we use cookies on our website. Cookies are very small files which a website uses to identify you when you come back to the site and to store details about your use of the site. Cookies are not malicious programs that access or damage your computer. We use cookies to improve the experience of people using our website.  
Third party sites  
Our site has links to other websites not owned or controlled by us. We are not responsible for these sites or the consequences of you going on to those sites.

May 2013
